-[birds chirping]
-[pensive music playing]
[Libby] I'm pretty hungry.
I hope we catch some fish soon.
[Matty] Me too.
-Okay, help me wind.
-Wind back?
-Can we turn this one?
-That's what I'm trying to do.
-[music concludes]
-Slowly. Slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly.
-I am doing it slowly.
-Okay, you got it.
Oh, Matty, look! You see that?
-See that big boat out there?
-[Matty] Mm-hmm.
[Libby] She is the prettiest boat
on Whidbey Island.
That's the Morning Star.
Someday when you're big enough,
I'm gonna teach you how to sail.
-It's the best thing there is, sailing.
-Better than fishing?
Yup. But you know what, kiddo?
-I don't think I want you to grow up.
-Why?
[Libby] What if you grow up
and marry some beautiful girl?
-Who's gonna go sailing with me then?
-Dad.
Not a chance.
-[light jazz music playing]
-[indistinct chatter]
Thank you so much.
[kids shouting indistinctly]
Nick. Uh. We need to talk.
Always happy to talk to you, Rudy.
-Hey, Warren.
-Uh-huh.
Did you get that notice
from First Seattle today?
Yeah. Yeah,
as a matter of fact, I did. [chuckles]
Good. Then you know.
-We've got a real problem.
-First Seattle is not a problem, Rudy.
These martinis are a problem. Do you mind?
-Not at all.
-Where were we? All right, First Seattle.
Mommy?
Hey, kiddo.
-How's it going?
-Hand off.
[both grunting]
Oh, you sack of potatoes. Ay-yi-yi.
Have you been carrying him
around the whole party?
-Yeah.
-We're never gonna marry you off, Angie.
Mm, yes.
Picasso.
-Blue period.
-[Nick] The artist's name is Kandinsky.
Wassily Kandinsky.
He was German,
of Russian extraction, 1866 to 1944.
And by the way,
Picasso's Blue period was figurative,
and ended in 1904.
And these watercolors are abstract,
done in 1911.
[scoffs] Picasso.
[indistinct chatter]
Everyone pipe down.
I'm about to give a speech.
Thank you for coming.
I always say the sign of a good party
is when I'm having a better time
than anyone else, but…
Now is the time
when you're expected to ante up…
For drinking all my liquor,
and eating all my food,
And spilling tomato sauce on my couch,
-Bobby Long.
-[guests] Ooh--
-What, you didn't think I saw you?
-[guests laughs]
-Oh, he's insufferable.
-[Nick] Now, we are here to raise…
-I know it.
-…a vast sum of money
for the Small Frye School.
So, while you are reaching
for your checkbooks,
it gives me great pleasure
to introduce Mrs. Rebecca Tingley,
Our totally ravishing,
and completely adorable headmistress.
[guests applauding, whistling]
Mr. Parsons, thank you. [chuckles]
First of all, I'd like to start
by introducing a few members
-of my staff to you today.
-Oh, God.
I give you our dedicated teacher
and head of admissions, Miss Angela Green.
-[guests cheering, applauding]
-Yay!
-[Matty speaking indistinctly]
-Me!
What are you thinking about?
-Was I always as rude as I am now?
-[giggles] Absolutely.
-[chuckles, kisses]
-[kisses]
Hi.
Come have a seat.
Angela, do you think
we ought to break the news to her?
I suppose it's better she hears it from us
than from someone else.
She's not gonna be happy about it.
What's up, guys?
Close your eyes.
Close 'em.
Okay, now, stand up.
Keep 'em closed.
-[humming]
-[light-hearted music playing]
Now, Libby, what is your favorite thing?
-Me?
-Not even close.
All right, open.
I heard Sean Gittman
was thinking of selling.
I made him an offer,
and he agreed
to let us take her out for the weekend.
And if you like it, it's yours.
-If I like it? [chuckles]
-Mm-hmm.
[Libby] Honey, we can't afford that.
[Nick] When have I ever let that
get in my way? Come on.
-[laughs]
-Huh?
What about Matty?
I'll take care of him.
We'll have a great time.
You hate to sail.
I can learn.
-[chuckles]
-Huh?
[both kiss]
[glorifying music playing]
Generally, wine like this
needs time to breathe.
But I don't know,
I don't think we should wait.
I don't see land.
So where is it?
Alaska's over that way,
Japan is straight ahead,
and Australia's somewhere to the left.
Where would you like to go?
Bed.
That can be arranged.
-[Libby sighing]
-[music concludes]
[Libby gasping, moaning softly]
[both giggling]
-[both grunt]
-[Libby moaning]
[breathing heavily]
-[chuckles, kisses]
-[kisses]
We should do this more often.
What do you mean?
Buy expensive sailboats?
-[chuckles]
-If this is what happens,
-I'll buy another one tomorrow.
-[chuckles]
No, go away, just the two of us,
with nobody else around.
[groans]
-I'll drink to that. [kisses]
-[kisses]
[indistinct banging, squeaking]
Nick?
Oh, my God. Nick?
-[shouting] Nick?
-[suspenseful music playing]
[whimpers]
Nick? Ni--
Oh, my God. [whimpers]
[waves crashing]
Nick? [whimpering]
[gasping, moaning]
[screaming] Nick! Nick!
Nick! [sobbing] Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
-[ship horn blaring]
-Nick?
[coast guard on P.A.]
Morning Star, this is the Coast Guard.
Put the knife down, ma'am, and step away.
I-- I don't-- I don't know--
I don't know where my husband is!
[reporter] …an around-the-clock search
for local businessman
Nick Parsons, who disappeared
in these waters off Whidbey Island.
-[motorboat engine revving]
-[indistinct chatter]
[cop] All right, tie it off.
-Hey, Cutter.
-[Cutter] Hey, Tom.
What have you got for me?
[indistinct chatter]
-[Libby] Anything?
-No.
Cutter, please don't let them give up.
He's very strong.
-[Cutter] Libby. L-- Libby.
-He's a very strong man.
[gasping]
The raft and life preservers
are all on board.
These guys,
they tracked the wind, currents--
Uh… Nothing.
The water temperature overnight
was 51 degrees.
-That's cold. That's really cold.
-[gasping, crying]
-Cutter, I can't breathe!
-Just put your head down.
Yeah, that's it.
Deep breaths. Big breaths.
-[cries]
-[shushes]
[waves crashing]
[indistinct chatter over radio]
-Mommy, look!
-[car doors slamming]
Hi, kiddo.
Hey, Bobby.
Hey, Libby. [sighs]
Um… Well Cutter, he, uh--
He asked me to come by
and talk to you, you know.
Just, um, not as an attorney,
just as a friend.
The inquest was held this morning,
and they reviewed all the evidence,
and Nick, uh, well,
he's officially been declared dead.
[Bobby] Now, Libby, they, um--
They've determined
it was a "wrongful death," and you--
Oh, Jesus, you-- you're being
formally charged with his murder.
-[laughs]
-[Bobby] I am here to advise you,
make no statements
whatsoever to the sheriff.
[Cutter] I'm sorry, Libby.
[Libby scoffing] Cutter!
Not in front of my kid, okay?
[tense music playing]
[keys jangling]
[music concludes]
I'm sorry, Libby.
Uh… The judge denied us bail.
[opening briefcase]
Can Angie keep looking after Matty?
Good. Okay, uh-- [sighs]
Let's, uh, take a look at this,
see what we can do.
Bobby. Here's what I think happened.
I had some wine, okay?
And I fell asleep.
It must have been the sun.
And maybe Nick was trying
to cut a snagged line or something,
because the knife
from the galley was on deck.
And-- and maybe the boat
pitched or something,
and he cut himself.
And he tried to come downstairs.
He tried to come below to wake me up.
[sighs]
[chuckles]
I quit these things when I met Nick.
It'll be all right. I promise you.
So.
Why don't we take a look
at this First Guarantee life?
Now…
You both bought life insurance policies
from the company around four months ago.
-And you are the beneficiary.
-I'm his wife.
Libby, you know this policy
is worth two million?
Nick wanted to make sure that
if anything happened to him, we'd be okay.
I'm afraid, he jury may feel
there's a big difference
between "okay" and two million dollars.
They may see it as a motive.
-Is that what they're saying out there?
-No, no one is saying that.
I don't think
we have to be concerned about--
That I killed Nick for money?
[scoffs]
I mean, I know we had some problems,
and Nick worried,
-But we were okay!
-[Bobby] Libby!
Two of his investors were suing him
for embezzlement.
First Seattle issued a lien
on all of his real estate properties,
Your personal possessions--
Now, Nick's death means
all these problems disappear
behind a corporate shield,
leaving you with two million dollars.
Do you think I killed him?
That's the first rule of being a lawyer.
What we think doesn't matter.
It matters to me.
No. Of course.
I don't think you killed him.
[prosecutor] Petty Officer Young,
what was the condition…
of the Morning Star's marine band radio
when you had a chance to inspect it?
The handset cord had been cut.
And as you initially
approached the sailboat,
what did you see?
Mrs. Parsons was holding a knife.
[audience murmuring]
I show you state's exhibit number four.
[Nick's voice on radio]
Uh… Mayday. Mayday.
This is, uh, the Morning Star.
[operator]
Sate your emergency, Morning Star.
[Nick] I've been stabbed.
I'm bleeding, uh-- Oh, Jesus.
My na-- my name's, uh, Nicholas Parsons.
-[operator] State your position?
-[Nick] I don't know, man.
Uh… Three miles northwest of,
uh, of Whidbey Island, I guess.
-Oh, God! Oh, God!
-[button clicks]
Mrs. Parsons, you've heard the testimony
presented to this court,
and your explanation is
that somebody must have
come aboard the Morning Star.
That's right.
Well, let's, uh,
consider all the possibilities.
Maybe a band of pirates.
Or aliens! Did aliens murder your husband?
No. Aliens weren't beneficiaries
in your husband's life insurance policy.
-Objection. Your honor, the prosecutor--
-Overruled.
-I told you what happened.
-Yes, you did.
-You told us, that you were asleep.
-Yes.
Maybe you were sleepwalking
when you stabbed your husband--
[Bobby] Objection. Please.
Is Miss Halliwell questioning the witness,
or making a closing argument?
Withdrawn.
I didn't kill my husband!
I loved my husband. [sobs]
[cries] Bobby, I did not kill my husband!
You have to believe me. [sobs echo, fades]
[telephone ringing]
I'm-- I'm sorry, Libby.
It's not your fault, Bobby.
[Matty hums]
[door closes]
I wanna ask you something, Angie.
I'd like you to adopt my son.
-No, Lib, I can't do that. Not to you.
-I've thought it through.
I barely survived my parents' house.
I'm not gonna put him there.
[Matty continues humming]
[Libby] Money won't be a problem
because there's the two million dollars
from the life insurance,
and it's going
into a trust fund in his name.
-It isn't about money.
-[whispers] I know.
-[Matty muttering softly]
-Matty loves you.
We can't let him become
a ward of the State.
[Matty mimics gunfire sounds]
[hums]
[softly] Thank you.
Hey, kiddo. Come see me.
-[chuckles]
-[dramatic music playing]
You're gonna go stay
with Angie for a while. Okay, kiddo?
Okay.
And you're gonna have lots of fun.
And I know
you're gonna be a good boy, right?
Yes, mommy.
And as soon as all this is over,
we'll be together again.
That's a promise, kiddo. Okay?
[pensive music playing]
I love you.
I love you, too.
[kisses]
[siren blaring]
[siren continues]
-[inmates chatting indistinctly]
-[music concludes]
-Who's this?
-[Evelyn] Rich bitch from Whidbey Island.
-She ain't gonna make it.
-What do you think? A year?
Five cartons says she offs herself
inside of six months.
-Deal.
-Get away from me.
Hey, take it easy.
We're your new best friends.
Heard you did your husband.
Probably deserved it.
Mine did.
[indistinct chatter, coughing]
[indistinct chatter, laughing]
[overlapping conversations]
[Libby]
I know what a pain it is to get here.
-I taught him how to say the ABC's.
-[Libby] Is that true?
-Sing it, Matty. Go!
-Yes.
Did you learn the alphabet, sweetie?
-Yeah.
-[Libby] Can you tell me?
-[sings] ♪ A, B, C, D E, F, G… ♪
-[laughs]
♪ H, I , J, K, L, M, N, O, P ♪
♪ Q, R, S T, U ♪
♪ W, X, Y and Z ♪
♪ Now I know my ABC's ♪
♪ Next time won't you sing with me ♪
[somber music playing]
-[phone line ringing]
-Give it up. Come on.
-Get off the phone, bitch. Jesus.
-[ringing continues]
[weeps]
[weeping continues]
-[indistinct chatter]
-[music concludes]
Whoa, you're low on cigarettes.
If you wanna make any friends,
I advise you buy another pack fast.
On account of your personality,
it ain't the best I've ever seen.
Hear you're tryin' to reach your friend,
the one with your boy.
Yeah, I can't find 'em.
They disappeared.
Oh, hon,
if you could disappear that easy,
believe you me,
I wouldn't be here right now.
-[chuckles] Me either.
-[whistle blowing indistinctly]
Think. Use your head.
There's gotta be a way to track 'em down.
[indistinct chatter, laughing continues]
-[receptionist] Small Fry School…
-[shushes]
-…front office.
-Hello, this is Angela Green calling.
-[receptionist] Angie, it's Jennifer.
-Yes, hi. How are you?
-[receptionist] Good to hear from you.
-Yes, it's nice to hear your voice.
Listen, I haven't gotten
a severance check in a while,
and I was hoping I could verify with you
that you have my correct mailing address
and phone number.
[receptionist] Sure, I'll check.
Can you hold on a sec?
Yes, of course. Thank you.
[indistinct chatter]
[receptionist] Yeah, I have it right here.
Tell me if this is right.
3-3-2-1 Mason Street,
San Francisco, 9-4-1-0-5.
The phone number is 4-1-5--
[telephone ringing]
-[telephone beeps]
-Hello?
-[Libby] Angie? Angie.
-Libby?
I--
I've tried to call you a thousand times.
-Is Matty okay? Where is he?
-[Angie] Yeah, he's fine.
Everything is fine.
What are you doing in San Francisco?
Put him on the phone.
Hey, why are you acting this way?
Because you disappeared,
and I haven't seen my son in a month!
-I was just about to call you.
-[Libby] Oh, bullshit!
How can you move
and not tell me, Angie?
We were coming to see you next week.
Just put Matty on the phone.
[sighs]
Matty? It's mommy. Come say hi.
Come here. Here.
-Hi, mommy.
-Hello, sweetie pie.
How are you, Matty?
[laughs]
I think about you all the time, honey.
I miss you so much.
Are you doing okay, kiddo?
I love you.
Listen, Matty.
I know that this has been really hard
but Angie is gonna bring you
up to see me next week, okay?
[Matty] Yes, mommy.
Daddy!
-[tense music playing]
-Nick?
[mouthing]
Nick?
-[indistinct chatter echoing]
-[shocked gasping]
[coins rattling]
[Nick sighing]
[line beeping]
[indistinct chatter echoing]
[music concludes]
He was in San Francisco last night.
I have a phone number,
but it's already been disconnected.
No, I don't--
I don't have a forwarding address.
He's gone.
Well, don't you have investigators?
Doesn't your company want
to get its two million dollars back?
Why aren't you listening to me?
I am innocent.
[prisoners yelling]
Yeah, you are. Sure, you are.
Hurry up.
["We Wish You A Merry Christmas" playing]
Put some elbow grease
behind that stirring.
-Nobody wants to eat any burnt tapioca.
-Does it smell like it's burning?
Oh, I swear you got shit for brains, girl.
You're in prison. Do you get that?
Nobody wants to listen
to anybody in prison,
so you can just forget
about reopening your case,
or a jail-house appeal. You got that?
They take years,
and they're 95% unsuccessful.
-So, if you want my advice--
-No.
Well, you're gonna get it.
You do your time.
So what are you now, a lawyer?
Once upon a time.
But they tend to disbar murderers.
And here's your Christmas present.
You ready?
Pay attention, because this is best
goddamn advice you ever gonna get.
Ever hear of double jeopardy?
Fifth amendment to the constitution?
Huh? No?
Well, double jeopardy provides that,
"No person may be tried
for the same crime twice." You got that?
Keep stirrin'. The state says
you already killed your husband.
They can't convict you
of it a second time.
That means that when you leave here,
you track him down,
and when you find him you can kill him.
That's right. You can walk
right up to him in Times Square,
put a gun to his head
and pull the fuckin' trigger,
and there's nothin'
anybody can do about it.
Kinda makes you feel
warm and tingly all over, don't it?
-[thrilling music playing]
-That's right. Keep stirrin'.
[grunting]
[exhales]
[thunderclap]
I gotta hand it to you, honey.
It's just sheer hate driving you on.
[music concludes]
Honey, the only way
you're gonna look like that
is if I staple the picture
to your forehead.
Just trust me, okay?
-Matty's eighth birthday, honey.
-[inmate 1] Aw.
-[everyone] Oh--
-[inmate 2] Look at that.
[indistinct chatter, laughter]
[inhales, blows]
[inmates cheering, applauding]
[light-hearted music playing]
You know, Evelyn,
I read that even if a child is separated
from its mother the day it's born,
it never forgets her voice.
Think that's true?
'Course I do.
"I feel like I've grown
these past six years."
"Grown"? Honey, they don't want to hear
that you've turned
into some kind of tree, okay?
So just repeat after me,
"If I could trade places
with my husband, I would."
Ugh. "If I could trade places
That's good. Now throw in a lot of
that born-again-Jesus stuff.
-They like that.
-Listen, listen, listen.
I want you to start with this--
"I'm not sitting in front of you today
to make excuses."
[Libby] I'm not sitting
in front of you today
to try to make any excuses.
I killed my husband.
I've had to live with that every day
for the past six years.
But I swear to you
that I'm a changed person.
Why should we believe you?
[Libby] I don't think
I can ask you to believe me.
All I can really do is believe in myself
and know that if I were given a chance,
I could do something good with my life.
Make up for the wrong I did.
-[indistinct chatter]
-[car horns blowing]
That was cool. Oh, mommy!
-Yeah!
-Hey, hey. Talk to me. [laughs]
Oh, man, did you see that?
[man speaking indistinctly]
…six years telling each other stories
about all the shit
that's been done to you.
A lot of shit's been done to you.
I know that.
But let's imagine that all those people
that did that shit showed up here.
-The man's across the hall.
-Thanks.
Let's imagine that they all showed up here
and apologized.
Would that change the situation
you're in right now?
[man speaking indistinctly]
-[commentator on TV indistinctly]
-Come in.
[commentator on TV indistinctly continues]
[sighs]
I'm Elizabeth Parsons.
What do you have in that box?
Elizabeth Parsons.
The State of Washington
has granted you a conditional parole.
For the next three years,
you will observe
all the rules of this facility,
which means no fighting,
no fornicating, no drinking, no drugs,
no exceptions, no excuses.
-Do you understand that?
-Yes.
This is your social security card.
You will find gainful
and sustained employment.
You are not to carry a firearm
or a weapon of any kind,
especially a knife.
Curfew is at 8:30.
This is my cell phone number.
Do not lose it.
If you think there's a chance
you will be even five minutes late,
you will call me,
I will have you picked up.
Do you understand that? Good.
Any violation of these conditions,
and your get-out-of-jail-free card
will be revoked by me,
and you will return to prison
to serve the remainder of your sentence
and maybe then some.
-Look right here.
-[camera shutter clicks]
[commentator on TV indistinctly]
[sighs, grunts]
-Is this a problem for you?
-No.
Yes, it is.
Do you want to tell me about him?
No.
[scoffs] No.
I'm gonna have trouble with you, Parsons.
No, sir. No, you're not.
I learned my lesson. I just want to--
I'm not interested
in your goddamn contrition.
I'm interested in your behavior.
Get out of here and behave yourself.
-You're in room eight on the second floor.
-[keys jingling]
No, you're, uh-- [chuckles]
You're never gonna get anywhere like that.
-Here.
-[keyboard keys clacking]
[beeps]
Hmm. Nice shampoo.
Now, uh, what are you looking for?
A friend I haven't seen
for a couple of years.
Someone said I should try the Internet.
This a boyfriend?
-Girl.
-Okay. Well, in that case, I'll help you.
[chuckles] Does your friend have e-mail?
-I have no idea.
-Okay, come on. Let's do some surfing.
-So, uh, what's your friend's name?
-Angela Green.
Uh… Zip code?
Hmm. How about a social security number?
That way we could run a credit report,
and it'll give us her address.
Nope. She was a school teacher.
-Done deal.
-[keyboard keys clacking]
-[man] And… voila.
-[beeps]
Now, maybe when this thing
has finished its searching,
we could go to this, uh,
this neat little bar I know
and, uh, you know, have a little drink.
What do you say?
Yeah. I just have to check in
with my parole officer first.
-You've been to jail?
-Actually, prison.
Jail is a different thing.
[laughing] So, what did you do,
not pay your parking tickets?
Oh, no.
I was convicted of murdering my husband.
[chuckling] You're kidding, right?
No, I'm not. Um… "Sliced and Diced,"
the paper called it. Can you believe that?
You're not kidding?
No. I said I wasn't.
But it would be nice to have a drink.
I haven't been out
in a long time. [chuckles]
Ye-- Oh!
Oh, look, I just remembered I have, um,
-this appointment with the--
-See ya.
See ya. Sorry.
Oh. Book. See ya. [clears throat]
[computer beeping]
Oh, my God. [sighs]
So he takes me out for dinner,
and he feeds me escargot.
-Do you know what those are? Snails.
-[gasps] Yeah.
Snails, yuck.
But anyway, the moment
I go to bed with him,
the big asshole dumps me. Gee, man.
[Ruby] Oh, for Christ's sake,
you nit-picking fuck!
[Travis] Ruby, do not insult me
by raising your voice.
I'm standing right here,
and I can hear you just fine.
-[Ruby] All right. Sorry.
-[Travis] By the way, I don't like it
I don't like it
when you call me dirty names.
[Ruby] Please, Mr. Lehman,
don't do this to me, man, okay?
I didn't do nothing!
[Travis] Where were you
this afternoon, Ruby?
[Ruby] I was-- I was at my job.
You were down on pike street
wearing lime-green hot pants
-and fishnet stockings!
-I was on my way to work!
-At McDonald's? In those clothes?
-Yes, that's right.
You haven't been to work in a week!
Get your stuff.
[Ruby] Look, I-- I'm sorry, man.
I won't do it again.
I will never do that shit again.
I promise that.
You blew off your parole.
You're going back. It's that simple.
[women sigh, groan]
You fuck! You fuckin' cocksucker!
-[Travis] You got a dirty mouth, Ruby!
-[Ruby] I want one chance!
I just want one chance!
Goddamn you, motherfucker!
You son of a bitch. You mean fucker.
You send me back there it'll kill me,
you mean son of a bitch!
-[guard] Come on.
-[Ruby] Fuck you! Fucking asshole!
-[all murmuring]
-Show's over. Go to sleep!
[indistinct chatter]
You think I'm a mean son of a bitch?
I think you could have
given her a second chance.
There are no second chances
in this house, baby.
This is the last-chance house.
You try to understand that.
[woman] Yeah. Yeah, we got it.
What the hell is wrong with that guy?
What I heard, the man used to be
some college whatchamacallit.
-Law teacher or something?
-Yeah, that's right. That's right.
You're kidding.
How does a law professor
end up someplace like this?
-'Cause life's a bitch.
-Bitch, my ass.
He got a D.U.I. And totaled his car.
I heard he totaled his wife
and his daughter in that accident.
Girl, you're talkin' shit.
Nobody got killed.
But by the time his wife
got done with him,
I bet he wished he was dead.
Took everything he had. Including the kid.
-Hasn't seen his girl in years.
-[tense music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
Libby, it's wrong of you to be here.
It's very wrong.
I'm sorry to bother you,
but you're my only hope.
-Sharon? No, you put that down, please.
-[children shouting indistinctly]
-Libby, I'm sorry. I can't.
-I want to find my son!
Matty's had six years with Angie.
I mean, think about it, Libby, six years.
Oh, Benjamin, that's a great sand castle.
If you come back into his life right now,
it's just gonna cause
more disruption and-- and pain.
Just think about it, Libby, please?
Think about it.
I just want to see him, Rebecca.
-[sighs]
-Can you give me an address for Angie,
-so I can see him?
-Look, I'm sorry. I really am sorry.
Lauren?
Come on, get down, please. That's it.
[footsteps approaching]
[dog barking]
[barking continues]
[knocking]
-Where's Parsons?
-[sighs] I don't know. Not here.
-[sighs, grunts]
-[file cabinet rattling]
[vehicle pulling up]
[gasps]
[ominous music playing]
[officer] Probably just a raccoon.
[cabinet, keys rattling]
[Libby panting]
[indistinct chatter over radio]
[officer] Check up the stairs.
[doorknob rattling]
[officer] Cutter! Up here!
Shit!
-[Libby grunting]
-[Cutter] I got her.
There she is.
[panting]
[grunts]
[both screaming]
-[Cutter] Shit!
-[both grunting]
[officer grunting]
-[screams, grunts]
-[music concludes]
Jesus Christ, Libby,
what are you doing here?
-[lock unlocking]
-[door opens]
-[door squeaking]
-[indistinct chatter over radio]
Did you have a nice day at the beach?
[buoy bell clanging]
You piss me off, Parsons.
Angela Green, that's the woman
that's got your kid, right?
Can we not talk, please, Lehman?
Okay. All right.
-So why'd she skip town?
-She just skipped town.
Yeah, with your husband, who isn't dead
'cause you didn't kill him? [chuckles]
-Bullshit.
-Okay, I killed my husband.
I chopped him up into little bits,
and dumped him piece by piece
in the Pacific.
-Are you satisfied?
-No. No.
You were a hell of a lot closer
to your kid three days ago
than you are today.
All you had to do was wait three years.
That's all. You fucking idiot.
You cannot know what it is like
to sit in prison for six years
and think of nothing else
in the world but your son.
Did I make the right choice?
You ask the wrong question, Lehman.
I didn't have a choice. Fuck your curfew!
Who's that? Your daughter?
Is that a problem for you, Lehman?
-[car engine turns off]
-I'm going up top.
[car door closing]
[bell ringing]
Don't go anywhere.
[ferry horn blows]
[indistinct chatter]
[indistinct chatter continues]
[woman] Janey, honey, read your book.
[engine starts]
[tires squealing]
Oh! Shit!
[chattering]
[indistinct chatter. laughter]
[thrilling music playing]
-[engine revs]
-[tires screeching]
[groans]
[gasps]
[grunting]
[screams]
-Oh, my God!
-[indistinct chatter]
[alarm blaring]
[alarm bell ringing]
[Travis grunting, gasping]
[both gasp]
[grunts]
-[screams]
-[groans, panting, gasping]
[indistinct chatter]
[gasps]
-[crew member 1] I got him!
-[crew member 2] Grab a hold for me.
[indistinct chatter]
[crew member 1] O2 ready.
-[man] Is he all right?
-[ferry crew] I guess he's all right.
[indistinct chatter]
[Karl] Did you voluntarily
give her the gun?
Come on, Karl.
What do you think? Hey! Hey.
-Sorry.
-Were you drinking?
-No, I wasn't drinking.
-It's been known to happen.
-Do you have any idea where she's gone?
-No.
All right. Well, that's about all,
then, isn't it?
-All what?
-[Karl clearing throat]
There'll be an investigation
into your actions today.
I wouldn't hold my breath
about the prospect of keeping your job.
Karl, give me a break. Goddamn.
[traffic whizzing]
[Libby] Thanks a lot.
[birds chirping]
[dirt scraping]
[Libby's Mother]
Sent your father off to the V.F.W.
He'll be playing gin for hours.
-Some things never change.
-[Libby's Mother] Oh!
He's not as bad
as he used to be, you know.
I'm glad for you, Mama.
[Libby's Mother grunts]
I always said
there was good money in tomatoes.
[laughs]
[traffic whizzing]
-[indistinct chatter]
-[soft music playing]
[salesman] So, you're in the market
for a BMW?
-Yeah. Who isn't?
-Well, they're the best.
I decided it was finally time to trade up.
Right.
So why don't you check my credit
and see if I can finance this.
Great. Let me have
your social security number,
and I'll get the ball rolling.
"20, Oriole Terrace, Evergreen, Colorado."
Is that your current address?
20, Oriole Terrace,
Evergreen, Colorado? Sure is.
Didn't you say your name was Angela Green?
-'Cause this says it's Angela Ryder.
-Oh, no. I said Ryder.
Angela Ryder.
What about the car?
[music concludes]
-[indistinct chatter]
-Here, fill this out and come back to me.
How's tricks, Orbe?
No way.
No way, no way.
I've been clean, Mr. Travis.
Oh, I know. I believe you. I do.
What I need is a search
on a lady named Angela Green.
I've got her social security number here.
I'd like you to--
Please. You know I'm not allowed
to give out personal information.
Oh, I'm so-- I shouldn't have
asked you that. I'm sorry.
Uh-huh.
Speaking of giving out
personal information,
does your employer know
you used to perform
the art of fellatio for a living,
went to prison for it,
-and now you're out on parole?
-Okay. Okay. Shut up.
-You're required by law to tell him.
-All right. Okay.
[sighs]
You're looking good, Orbe.
I know.
[orchestral music playing]
-[music fades]
-[intense music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[dog barking in the distance]
[doorbell rings]
[pistol clicks]
[Sam's mother] Honey, can you get that?
Hi.
-[Sam's mother] Who is it, Sam?
-[Sam] Uh… Some lady.
[music concludes]
May I help you?
I'm looking for my friend, Angela Ryder.
I thought this was her address.
I've never heard of her.
But we've just moved in.
Uh… Maybe you should check
with the woman who lives next door.
She's been here 40 years.
[Libby] Excuse me.
Dearie, whatever you're selling,
I've already got two of them.
[chuckles] I'm just looking
for my friend, Angela Ryder.
She used to live next door.
Oh, I--
I'm sorry to be the one to tell you,
but Angie died in the accident.
It was three or four years ago.
It was one of those awful things.
The, uh, stove, the gas stove
in their house was leaking.
The explosion knocked out
some of my windows,
-and, uh--
-What about the boy?
Matty? He's such a dear child.
No, he and Simon
weren't there when it happened.
Poor Simon.
I've never seen anyone
so… grief stricken.
Oh, I'm sure.
-[indistinct chatter]
-[indistinct announcements over P.A.]
-[somber music playing]
-[whirring, clicking]
[indistinct chatter]
Help me out, kiddo.
It would really help if you could remember
what kind of car she was driving.
-Well, it was an old truck.
-Yeah?
It's, um-- I don't know
what year or make or anything.
Well, what color was it?
[indistinct chatter]
Kandinsky?
It's a bit out of our reach, I'm afraid.
I have a few Picasso
and Chagall lithographs.
-[music concludes]
-Mm, no. It… it's Kandinsky
that I'm particularly interested in,
especially his Blue Rider period.
I love that.
Uh… Well, um… [smacks lips]
Let's check Art Scan.
Kandinskys don't become available
too often, I'm afraid.
Uh… Here's a lovely little Miro.
-It's quite reasonable.
-It really needs to be Kandinsky.
Kandinsky… yes.
Ah! Here is a lovely
1922 Kandinsky lithograph.
-It's not quite the--
-The 1911 is all that interests me.
1911…
[traffic whizzing]
-Stop. There. Yes. Yes, that's it.
-[salesman] What?
I'm afraid we've missed that.
It was sold to a museum
in Munich six months ago.
Do you think you could find who sold it?
Perhaps they have more.
Well, uh, why, yes. Yes, let's see.
-Ah…
-[bell dings]
If you'll excuse me a moment.
Yes, sir. Can I help you?
Well, yes. My name is Travis Lehman…
[dramatic music playing]
[Travis] Actually, I'm looking
for a young lady…
[beeps]
-[car engine starting]
-[window shatters]
[tires squealing]
[indistinct clamor]
-[tires screeching]
-[car horns honking]
[pants]
[tires screeching]
She seemed so refined.
I would really like to know
what that woman wanted in your gallery.
-[pants]
-[music concludes]
[airplane engine whirring]
[group singing acapella] ♪ Amazing grace ♪
-[indistinct chatter]
-[group] ♪ How sweet ♪
♪ The sound ♪
♪ That saved ♪
♪ A wretch ♪
♪ Like me ♪
[mellow music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
Can I help you?
[music concludes]
I'm looking for Jonathan Devereaux.
Mr. Devereaux is out right now.
He'll be back tonight for the party.
Well, is Matty here?
I don't believe I know you, ma'am.
Maybe you'd like to leave a message.
[indistinct chatter]
-[traffic whizzing]
-[car horn honks]
-[indistinct chatter]
-[hotel lobby music playing]
[receptionist] It's certainly a pleasure
having you stay with us
-here at the Monteleone, Mrs. Kritch.
-[Mrs. Kritch] Thank you.
-My suite has a view?
-Your room has a lovely view, Mrs. Kritch.
-And I need a masseuse.
-I'll send Jerome right up.
Bruce?
1420, Mrs. Kritch.
Hello.
I'm sorry. Are you lost?
No. Actually, I'm found.
I just had an hour with Jerome.
Oh. Jerome.
I've heard that he is marvelous.
He's fabulous.
I haven't felt this good
since my husband died.
So, I've got something for tonight,
but I think I need Armani.
Yes. Very good, Mrs…
Kritch. Suite 1420.
Of course.
I'll be charging it to my room.
-[computer beeps]
-Hm. Now, Mrs. Kritch,
I would say that you are a size… four?
-A two.
-Of course.
[indistinct chatter]
There's a guy waiting for you.
Did you catch that thing?
What did you use for bait?
I caught that big bucket-mouth
son of a bitch
off an old rebel lure my daddy left me.
'Course there's buzz bombs, poppers, jigs,
all kinds of things
work back in these waters.
I'm Jim Mangold.
Travis Lehman,
Washington Department of Corrections.
[Jim] What can I do for you?
-[exhales] Who's this?
-That's somebody I'm looking for.
Pretty girl.
Oh, yeah. She's very pretty,
for a convicted murderer. [chuckles]
She jumped parole on me.
[smacks lips] Mr. Lehman,
I'd love to be able to help you, sir.
No, I don't want you guys
to go to any trouble.
I can handle matters. I just came down
as a professional courtesy,
since she's in New Orleans,
and came here to kill
one of your prominent citizens.
And just how is she planning
on doing that?
I don't know. She'll probably use
the .38 special she stole from me.
[shouts] Roy Lee!
Get these in the works now.
-[guest] She looks lovely.
-Invitation, please.
Enjoy your evening.
Good evening. Thank you.
-[indistinct chatter]
-[jazz music playing]
[doorman] Invitations, please.
Yes, I need to see your invitation.
Thank you.
Enjoy your evening.
Your invitation?
[guest] Oh, thank you.
-[doorman] Good evening.
-What a remarkable wrap.
Where on earth did you find that?
The First Lady asked me the same thing
when we stayed at the White House,
-and I wouldn't tell her either.
-[both laugh]
-[doorman] Your invitation, sir?
-I got it right here.
Enjoy your evening.
-Good evening, miss.
-Good evening.
♪ Mention of work makes you go berserk ♪
♪ 'Cause you hate to do a stitch ♪
♪ If you're so smart
How come you ain't rich? ♪
♪ You're out for a ride
On the road to fame ♪
♪ Yet you wind up in a ditch ♪
♪ If you're so smart
Tell me, how come you ain't rich? ♪
♪ Hershey started with a chocolate bar
Wrigley with a stick of gum ♪
♪ Planters took his peanuts
And travelled far ♪
♪ Now tell me what you doin', chum? ♪
♪ I been hearin'
All about all your big ideas ♪
♪ Since you started. What's the hitch? ♪
♪ If you're so smart
How come you ain't rich? ♪
♪ How come you ain't rich? ♪
-[music concludes]
-[guests applauding]
-Good evening, mesdames and messieurs.
-[guests] Good evening!
We're delighted to witness this evening
on this very special occasion
and, as is the custom in New Orleans,
since even before the war
of Northern Aggression…
[guests laughing, applauding]
…we offer the ladies of this fair city
our first bachelor to be placed
up on the auction block,
our host, Jonathan Devereaux.
[guests cheering, applauding]
[Louis] Where is that man?
Where is that man?
-Hey, Jonathan.
-Thank you, Louis.
-You all having a good time?
-[guests] Yeah!
Now then, ladies, uh,
what you see before you
is a moderately
presentable man in his thirties,
given to unhealthy thoughts
and a dissipated lifestyle.
[ladies laughing]
With, and this is what's gonna
cost you the really big money.
[guests cheering, applauding]
-Absolutely no redeeming moral virtue.
-[guests laughing]
Five hundred.
Dear woman, my cuff links
cost more than that.
-[guests laughing]
-Do I hear a 1,000?
-A thousand.
-Thank you.
-Ooh!
-[guests applauding]
-Mm!
-Two thousand.
[guests gasping, applauding]
All right, now, did I just hear the voice
of the charming Miss Monroe?
'Cause I was just starting to worry,
beginning to think you didn't care.
[Libby] Twenty-five hundred.
[guests gasping]
Twenty-five hundred. We have a new bidder.
-Twenty-five hundred.
-Three thousand.
[guests applauding]
-Five thousand.
-[guests gasping]
[applauding]
Fifty-five hundred.
[guests hooting, murmuring]
We have 5,500. Will, uh,
will the lady take us to six?
Ten thousand dollars.
[guests exclaiming]
[applauding]
Well, see, at last,
someone who knows my true value.
-[guests laughing]
-[Nick] Now, Miss Monroe,
I believe the bid
is to you at 10,500 dollars.
Well, you can have him, honey.
Believe me, he ain't worth that much.
I know from personal experience.
-[guests exclaiming]
-Yeah. Thank you, honey.
All right, going once.
Going twice.
-Sold to the woman in the back.
-Sold!
-[guests applauding]
-[Nick] Ten thousand dollars.
Would you like to come forward
and claim your prize, young lady?
[dramatic music playing]
Hello, Nick.
Well, aren't you gonna give me a kiss?
I think I've earned it.
[guests murmuring, booing]
[applauding]
-And now…
-I'll make this real easy for you, Nick.
I'll make you an offer you can't refuse.
You used to love a good deal, didn't you?
-Can we just take this someplace private?
-I don't think so.
I remember what happened
the last time we were alone.
-I don't believe we've met.
-[sighs]
-I'm Suzanne Monroe.
-I'm Libby. I'm his wife.
Well, Jonathan!
A minute ago a bachelor,
and now you're married.
You don't waste any time.
-You been in New Orleans long?
-She's, uh--
I'm just passing through town
to pick up my child.
-I'll be leaving very soon.
-How nice.
We're finally putting the past behind us
and moving on with our lives,
-aren't we, Jonathan?
-Sure.
I do have one question though.
How long were Angie and you fucking
before you decided to get rid of me?
[clears throat]
Would you excuse us, please?
Oh, yeah, sure. Go ahead.
-Where is he, Nick?
-Libby. Libby--
You destroyed my life,
and I will destroy yours
unless you give me Matty.
That's all I want.
[Nick] Listen,
let me explain something to you.
You have to understand something.
We were going under.
We were gonna lose everything.
If I'd had any guts,
I would have killed myself,
but I was trying to protect you.
That's why I got the life insurance.
So I would be out of the picture
and you and Matty would be okay.
And I just never believed
they would convict you.
They did, Nick.
And the thing with Angie happened later.
It was just-- It was a nightmare.
And the worst part of it
was being away from you.
So is that why you killed her?
-[guests applauding]
-[chuckles]
-That was an accident.
-Nice try, Nick. I'm not buying.
It's bullshit.
-I will swear on the life of our son.
-Oh, don't you fucking dare.
[scoffs] You can keep your hotel,
your fancy accent and your new name.
-Just give me Matty.
-I understand.
No. Now.
-Give him to me now.
-Libby, it's the middle of the night.
-I can't just walk away from here.
-[Libby] Do you think I'm stupid?
-No. I don't think you're stupid.
-I won't let you slip away once again.
It's too far to Matty's school.
-And you've got to be patient.
-I've been patient for six years.
-[bidder] Do I hear 2,000?
-I want my child.
Ah! Thank you. You're a beautiful woman.
I'll call you tomorrow, Nick.
No screwing around.
[bidder] Going twice.
Okay, 2,000 for the lady in red.
[Travis] Excuse me.
Do you know where Mr. Devereaux is?
-[waiter] He's at the bar, sir.
-Over here?
-[waiter] Yes, sir.
-Thank you.
[bidder] You ready to spend
some more money?
Who's gonna start us off? Who's gonna go?
[guests applauding]
I'm sorry. Oh, thank you, Marcel.
-Can I offer you a drink?
-Oh, no thanks.
Wait a second. Let me guess.
I take you for scotch and soda.
-Huh?
-Well, I'll have a Diet Coke, please.
Well, all right, but I bet you used
to drink and now you're on the wagon.
Ten dollars says I'm right.
You sure you've never seen
this woman before?
-No, I'm positive.
-Okay.
Let me get it straight, though.
She believes that I am her husband.
-Oh, yeah.
-Whom she killed.
Yes, sir.
That's… that's pretty far-fetched.
Uh… Far-fetched or not,
she is in New Orleans,
She does have a gun
and she is looking for you.
Well, thank you.
I'll alert our security people.
-You do that.
-[thunder rumbling]
-[indistinct chatter]
-[Cajun music playing]
Cops have been passing these out.
No reward. Screw 'em.
You're gonna be posted
in every hotel in town.
So much for a good night's sleep.
Take this. Get out of here.
Thanks a lot.
[Dixieland music playing]
Let's go, Lehman. We spotted your girl.
[bells clanging]
-[thunder clapping]
-[horse whinnies]
Where'd she go, Dilbert?
Hey!
-Hey!
-I'm sorry.
-What do you think you're doing?
-I'm very sorry, ma'am.
I thought you were somebody else.
It was a case of mistaken identity.
-Have a good evening.
-I take it that ain't her.
[music concludes]
[indistinct chatter]
-[Nick] Mr. Lehman.
-[chuckles]
Come in.
-Thank you.
-May I offer you a Cuban cigar?
Oh, no thanks.
Well, as you can see,
I'm alive and kicking.
[chuckles] Yeah.
So what can I do for you this morning?
We spotted the Parsons woman
in the quarter last night.
She got away. I just came by
to find out if you'd heard from her.
Not a peep.
Do you have any idea
why she's fixated her lunacy on you?
Well, the world's full of crazy people,
am I right?
Oh, yes, you are right. [laughs]
Truer words were never spoken.
Those are nice pictures there.
Did your kids do them?
Uh… No. [chuckles]
Those pictures are by
a very great artist named Kandinsky.
Oh.
But why do I think you already knew that?
[telephone ringing]
Excuse me for a second.
Yes?
This is a business call.
Oh, I'm sorry. [chuckles]
I hope you'll excuse me.
You let yourself out that back door.
It leads down to the kitchen.
Yeah. Get the chef to fix you
a fabulous New Orleans breakfast.
-Thanks.
-[Nick] I recommend the Eggs St. Jacques.
-Oh, boy. That sounds good.
-[Nick] Mm-hmm. I have your card.
Okay.
Morning, darling.
I hope you had a nice night.
I want you to bring Matty
to Lafayette Cemetery number three.
A cemetery?
That's an odd choice for a reunion.
It's a big tourist place, Nick.
Lot of people around.
You're a smart girl.
I can have him there by 4:00.
[jazz band playing "St. James Infirmary"]
[indistinct chatter]
Where's Matty?
Relax. He's-- He was nervous.
So I just told him
he could go play inside.
There he is.
Matty? Come over here, son.
Oh, geez. Matty--
-Okay, I'll get him for you.
-No! No.
That's something I want to do.
Matty?
Hey, kiddo.
Hey, Matty!
Matty?
[stammers] Matty, it's mommy.
[gasps, groans]
[Jim] Mr. Lehman,
you're gonna have to learn to relax, son.
What have you got your panties
in such a twist about, anyhow?
-[keyboard clacking]
-[sighs]
You ever arrest anybody
you thought was innocent, Mangold?
Nope.
-[computer beeping]
-[Travis sighs]
'Course there's no information
on Jonathan Devereaux
that's over three years old.
-Three years ago the guy didn't exist.
-So he changed his name.
Lots of folks change their names, Lehman.
-That don't make 'em criminals.
-Yeah, but I'm betting
he changed it from Simon Ryder,
and before that, Nick Parsons.
-But you can't prove it.
-No.
[band playing "Red River Valley"]
[indistinct chatter]
Hey! Is that long distance?
Bill me. Lucy, hi. This is Travis. Listen.
I want you to get the D.M.V. to fax me
a Washington driver's license photograph
of one Nicholas Parsons.
I'm at the New Orleans Police Department.
Travis, you better talk
-to Mr. Carruthers.
-Travis!
-His colon is twisted in a knot.
-Give me that.
I've had to cover
your office for you, Travis.
-Where the hell are you?
-Listen to me, Karl.
I think maybe this Parsons woman
has been telling the truth.
[Karl] You're not
a law professor anymore, Travis.
You're barely even a parole officer.
-So stop playing Mission Impossible and--
-[Travis] All I need
is a D.M.V. Driver's license photograph
of Nicholas Parsons.
You get back here today,
because tomorrow,
you're going in front of the commission.
Karl, I know I'm right.
You give me a chance, okay?
Now, I'm asking you politely.
You send me the goddamn picture!
-[Libby groans]
-[lighter flicking]
[sniffs]
[gasps, pants]
[eerie music playing]
[whimpers]
[pants]
[moans]
-[casket pounding]
-[Libby grunting]
[grunts]
-[gunshot]
-[Libby grunts]
[grunts]
Hey!
-[door pounding]
-[Libby] Hey!
[grunts]
-[printer humming]
-[indistinct chatter]
It's not him.
[Jim] See, Lehman, the thing is,
every now and again,
we all want to believe in something.
But we just keep forgetting
that 99.9% of the time,
life just flat don't work out.
I hadn't thought of that, Mangold.
Thanks. I feel a lot better now.
Any time, hoss. Any time.
-[indistinct chatter]
-[tense music playing]
Hold it. Hold it right here.
[sighs]
[gasps]
-It's over, Libby.
-[music fades]
-[solemn music playing]
-[sobs] Oh, Travis.
[wails]
[indistinct chatter]
Messages.
Thank you.
-[Travis] Mr. Devereaux?
-Mr. Lehman.
I'm sorry. This is really not a good time.
I understand.
You know a lot of people
feel that way about me.
-But I have good news.
-Mm-hmm?
Won't take long.
-Well?
-Well…
Turns out I owe you
an apology, Mr. Devereaux.
After our last conversation
I started thinking
maybe that Parsons woman is telling
the truth about who you used to be.
So I asked the Washington State
Department of Motor Vehicles
to send me a driver's license photograph
of Nicholas Parsons.
-And?
-And this is what came up.
[laughs]
Well…
we all make mistakes.
There's no harm done.
[Travis] Then I thought about it
some more, and it occurred to me
what a common name Nicolas Parsons is.
You know, it turns out there were six.
And this…
was number three.
I never liked that picture.
So, Mr. Lehman,
you came here to make a deal
otherwise, I guess you would have
gone straight to the police.
-So, question is, what's your price?
-A million dollars.
-[laughs]
-It's a nice round figure, right?
Uh…
All right. But you're gonna have
to give me a couple of days.
No way. One million dollars, right now.
Mr. Lehman, it's nine o'clock at night.
I can't just-- [snaps fingers]
-Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait.
-[keypad beeps]
I have 100,000 dollars in the safe here.
And you can have that now.
I'll get you the rest tomorrow.
You got a deal.
We do have one other problem,
and that's Mrs. Parsons.
She could still make
a lot of trouble for us, even from prison.
-[chuckles] And I really don't need that.
-Well, I think I've solved that problem.
What do you mean?
Let's just say the problem
has been buried.
-Really?
-She's gone, I promise you.
[tense music playing]
You're not very good
at keeping promises, Nick.
You gonna do something?
What are you talking to me for?
She's the one with the gun.
They're tough in Louisiana, Libby.
You shoot me,
they'll give you the gas chamber.
No, they won't.
It's called double jeopardy.
I learned a few things in prison, Nick.
I could shoot you in the middle
of Mardi Gras and they can't touch me.
As an ex-law professor,
I can assure you she is right.
Where's my son?
In St. Albans School
in Georgia, all right?
You have your son back.
You got what you want.
[gunshot]
[music concludes]
I haven't felt that good
in six years. [laughs]
I don't want to kill you, Nick.
I just want you to suffer like I suffered.
What she means, Nick, is,
you're going to prison…
for murder.
-Who did I supposedly murder?
-Me.
-All you've got is an old fax photo.
-Which supplies the motive.
Your wife, whom you had framed,
tracks you down,
and to keep her
from exposing you, you kill her.
-You won't get away with it.
-[tape rewinding]
[Nick's voice on tape]
Well, I think I've solved that problem.
-[Travis] What do you mean?
-[Nick] Let's just say
the problem has been buried.
-[Travis] Really?
-[Nick] She's gone, I promise you.
[clicks off]
Taped confessions are very persuasive
in court, Nick,
and of course
there is the physical evidence
that we're gonna put
in the trunk of your car.
A shovel, hair, my fingerprints,
a little blood.
Don't forget the gasoline.
It'll look like you burned
and buried my body,
just like you say on the tape.
The prosecution rests.
You better get out of here.
Nobody wants a dead woman
walking around when the police
are trying to arrest a guy for her murder.
Wait a minute. I'll take that gun.
-[gunshot]
-[gasps]
[intense music playing]
-[gunshots firing]
-[pants]
[groans]
No. [gasps]
-[Travis grunts]
-[glass shatters]
[both grunt]
[Travis grunts]
-[Nick grunts]
-[groans]
[pants]
[gunshot]
[music concludes]
[indistinct chatter]
Well, Lehman, you gonna live?
-[Jim laughing]
-I doubt it.
Ms. Parsons,
since you are still legally his wife,
I expect you just inherited yourself
a right fine little hotel here.
Not interested.
[groans]
I guess I'm gonna take off now.
No. No, you're not.
You're a parole violator.
You're in my custody.
You're going with me to Seattle,
-where I will demand a full pardon…
-[chuckles]
…and a parade, and a little pink poodle…
-on a keychain.
-[laughs]
-[birds chirping]
-[indistinct chatter]
[student shouting] Come on, Ryan, pass it!
[whistle blows]
What are you waiting for?
Go on.
I don't know if I've ever been
so scared in my whole life.
I think a big part of me never thought
I'd\ really find him.
What if he doesn't recognize me?
-I mean, maybe after all this time--
-Damn, woman!
Because of you, I have lost
a perfectly good used car,
and a not-so-good job.
If you don't go to this kid right now,
I'm gonna have you arrested for stupidity.
Go on.
[inhales, sighs softly]
Thanks, Lehman.
-You saved my life.
-[Travis chuckles]
You saved mine too.
[indistinct clamor]
-Coach Matthews. How you doing?
-Nice to meet you.
It'll be halftime soon.
[soft music playing]
-[whistle blows]
-[Coach Matthews] Halftime!
Matty.
[soft music playing]
Hi.
Do you know who I am?
[chuckles] They told me you were dead.
[gasps]
No, sweetheart.
[exhales]
[chuckles]
[music concludes]
[instrumental music playing]
-[music fades]
-[dramatic music playing]
-[solemn music playing]
[music concludes]